

9824731830



Meet Rakholiya

meetrakholiya.dev@gmail.com



Surat, Gujarat



Full Stack Web Developer & SEO

SUMMARY

Broadly and deeply knowledgeable in A wide variety of computer languages with 1 year+ Experience As well as the principles and techniques Of website construction and maintenance. Dedicated to delivering impactful results through a proactive approach to any challenge.

EDUCATION

12th Commerce

P.P Savani Vldhyalay -2020 - 21 Percentage: 80%

Gujarat University

Bachelor of Computer Applications -2021 - 24 CGPA: 7.20

SKILLS

- Technical Skills: Javascript, PHP, HTML5, CSS3, Rest Api
- Framework: Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Reactjs
- Database: MySql
- CMS: WordPress, Headless WordPress, Custom Theme, Plugin, Custom Blocks, Flementor and Woocommerce
- SEO

LANGUAGES

- English
- Hindi
- Gujarati

CERTIFICATIONS

 Completion Certificate Of Theme Development Course of BitDegree

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

- Adbrains Technology, Surat
- Role: Full Stack Web Developer 07/2024 - Present
- Vijayho Multimedia, Surat
- Role: Internship 02/2024 - 06/2024
- Genuin Codebase LLP, Ahmedabad
- Role: CONTENT CREATOR AND PRODUCTION 03/2023 03/2024

PROFESSIONAL PROJECTS

- Ice Stabilizer Website (Ecommerce)
- Vedicana (Ecommerce)
- Custom BlockTheme
- 7 sense bath (Ecommerce)
- Evergreen Nursery BCA Final Year Project
- Digital Marketing Website and many more.....

HOBBIES

- Explore new places
- Cricket
- Listen songs